Inventory of the Arthur Kemp papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Herbert Hoover Subject File, 1922-1952 (Box 7-11)
  - Winn, H. Oscar, and S. Q. Sevier. Letters and legal brief, 1929-1933 (Folder 11: 10)
    Includes letters by J. Edgar Hoover re investigation of these individuals
- New Deal Subject File, 1928-1952 (Box 11-12)
  Notes, memoranda, printed matter, and typed transcripts from printed sources, relating to the New Deal and used as research material for the Magnum Opus of Herbert Hoover
  - American Liberty League
    - General. Notes and clippings, 1934-1952 (Folder 11: 11)
    - American Liberty League issuances. Press releases, printed speeches, brochures, and pamphlets, 1934-1936 (Folder 11: 12)
  - Collectivism. Notes, memoranda, typed excerpts from printed sources, and printed matter, 1932-1951 (Folder 12: 1)
  - Communism and New Deal. Notes, typed excerpts from printed sources, clippings, bulletins, flyers, and pamphlets, 1935-1939 (Folder 12: 2)
  - Democratic Party National Committee--Campaign contributions, 1928-1952 (Folder 12: 3)
  - Glass, Carter. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1933-1939 (Folder 12: 4)
  - Johnson, Hugh S. Speeches, printed articles, and clippings, 1935-1938 (Folder 12: 5)
  - Jones, Jesse H. Typed excerpts from printed sources, and pamphlet, 1943-1951 (Folder 12: 6)
  - Moley, Raymond. Typed excerpts from printed sources, memorandum, and clipping, 1939-1948 (Folder 12: 7)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
    - General. Clippings and printed articles, 1932 (Folder 12: 8)
    - Quotations. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1932-1941 (Folder 12: 9)
- Communist Subversion Subject File, 1927-1955 (Box 13-15)
  Correspondence, memoranda, notes, printed matter, and typed transcripts from printed sources, relating to communist subversion in the United States and used as research material for the Magnum Opus of Herbert Hoover
  - General
    - Memoranda, notes, letters, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1948-1955 (Folder 13: 1)
    - Clippings and printed articles, 1935-1955 (Folder 13: 2-3)
    - Congressional Record excerpts, 1945-1952 (Folder 13: 4)
    - Pamphlets, 1934-1951 (Folder 13: 5)
      Includes The Anti-Defamation League and Its Use in the World Communist Offensive; Is the American Youth Congress a Communist Front?; The Red Record of Senator Harvey Kilgore
    - Serial issues, 1946-1955 (Folder 13: 6)
  - Amerasia. Clippings, 1950 (Folder 14: 1)
  - Budenz, Louis F. Page proofs of Budenz's book The Cry Is Peace, memorandum, and clippings, 1951-1952 (Folder 14: 2)
  - Burgum, Edwin B. Letters and leaflet, 1952 (Folder 14: 3)
  - Communist Party issuances. Speech transcript, printed articles and pamphlets, 1927-1945 (Folder 14: 4)
    Includes America's Decisive Battle. See also Oversize File
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations. Political Action Committee. Memorandum, undated (Folder 14: 5)
  - Constitutional Educational League. Bulletins and pamphlet (Native Nazi Purge Plot), 1938-1951 (Folder 14: 6)
  - Dies, Martin. Letter, speech transcript, clipping, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1941-1951 (Folder 14: 7)
  - Dulles, John Foster. Letter and memorandum by H. L. Hunt, 1953 (Folder 14: 8)
  - Frankfurter, Felix. Memorandum, leaflet, and clipping, 1939-1948 (Folder 14: 9)
  - Gitlow, Benjamin. Typed excerpts from printed sources and clipping, 1939-1948 (Folder 14: 10)
  - Hiss, Alger. Memoranda, clippings, printed articles, typed excerpts from testimony, and photocopies of Pumpkin Papers documents, 1938-1953 (Folder 14: 11)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations. Circulated documents, typed excerpts from testimony, memoranda, printed article, and clipping, 1940-1953 (Folder 14: 12)
  - Jordan, G. Racey. Clippings, 1949-1952 (Folder 14: 13)
  - Joy, Henry B. Booklet (Reference Material...with Reference to Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America...), 1936 (Folder 14: 14)
  - League of American Writers. Press releases, letter, typed excerpts from printed sources, clippings, and Congressional report, 1941-1943 (Folder 15: 1)
  - Long, Hamilton A. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1950 (Folder 15: 2)
  - Lyons, Eugene. Printed article and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1941-1951 (Folder 15: 3)
  - National Electric Light Association. Booklet (The Radical Campaign against American Industry), 1930 (Folder 15: 4)
  - Pace, John T. Letter, printed testimony and typed excerpts from printed testimony re 1932 Bonus March, 1949-1951 (Folder 15: 5)
  - Reuther, Walter. Circulated report, 1949 (Folder 15: 6)
  - United Nations. Clippings and printed articles, 1950-1954 (Folder 15: 7)
  - White, Harry Dexter. Memorandum, clippings, and printed articles, 1953 (Folder 15: 8)
- World War II Subject File, 1923-1955 (Box 15-34)
  Correspondence, memoranda, notes, printed matter, and typed transcripts from printed sources, relating to World War II and used as research material for the Magnum Opus of Herbert Hoover. See also Oversize File
  - General
    - General. Letter, memoranda, notes, typed excerpts from printed sources, and printed matter, 1948-1955 (Folder 15: 9)
    - Baldwin, Hanson W. Printed articles and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1949-1950 (Folder 15: 10)
    - Barnes, Harry Elmer. Letter, pamphlets, and clippings, 1950-1952 (Folder 15: 11)
    - Bradley, Omar N. Memorandum, typed excerpts from printed sources, and clipping, 1951 (Folder 15: 12)
    - Clark, Mark W. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1950 (Folder 15: 13)
    - Conn, Stetson, and Louis Morton. Letters, typed excerpts from printed sources, and clipping, 1953-1954 (Folder 15: 14)
    - Fuller, J. F. C. Memorandum and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1949 (Folder 15: 15)
    - King, Ernest J. Memoranda, 1952 (Folder 15: 16)
    - Marshall, George C. Memoranda, printed articles, typed excerpts from printed sources, and clippings, 1944-1951 (Folder 15: 17)
    - Noel, Leon. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1948-1949 (Folder 15: 18)
    - Patton, George S. Clippings, 1951-1952 (Folder 15: 19)
  - China
    - General. Memorandum and flyer, 1941-1950 (Folder 16: 1)
    - Chennault, Claire. Memoranda and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1949 (Folder 16: 2)
    - Feis, Herbert. Memoranda and printed excerpts, 1953 (Folder 16: 3)
    - Hurley, Patrick. Memoranda, undated (Folder 16: 4)
  - Chronology
    - 1919-1938. Memoranda, notes, and printed matter, 1935-1950 (Folder 16: 5)
    - 1939. Memoranda, notes, typed excerpts from printed sources, clippings, printed articles, and speeches, 1939-1951 (Folder 16: 6)
    - 1940. Memoranda, notes, speeches, clippings, flyers, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1940-1947 (Folder 16: 7)
    - 1941. Memoranda, notes, clippings, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1941-1946 (Folder 16: 8)
    - 1942. Memorandum, clipping, and typed excerpts from printed sources (Folder 17: 1)
    - 1943. Memoranda, notes, clipping, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1943-1954 (Folder 17: 2)
    - 1944. Excerpts from printed sources (Folder 17: 3)
    - 1945. Memoranda, notes, clippings, printed articles, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1945-1952 (Folder 17: 4)
  - Conferences
    - Yalta Conference, 1945 February
      - General. Memoranda, clippings, printed articles, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1947-1956 (Folder 17: 5-6)
      - The Conferences at Malta and Yalta, 1945 (uncorrected galleys of United States Department of State publication), 1955 (Folder 17: 7-8)
      - Leahy, William D. Memorandum, clipping, printed articles, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1950 (Folder 18: 1)
      - Stettinius, Edward R. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1949 (Folder 18: 2)
    - Inter-American Conference on Problems of War and Peace, Mexico City, 1945 March (Folder 18: 3)
    - United Nations Conference on International Organization, San Francisco, 1945 April-June (Folder 18: 4-6)
    - Potsdam Conference, 1945 July-August (Folder 18: 7)
      Clippings, printed articles, and typed excerpts from printed sources
  - Food relief
    - General
      - Press releases, 1940 October (Folder 19: 1)
        Includes related correspondence. See also Herbert Hoover Speeches and Writings/Press release on food relief to Europe, 1940 October 7
      - Statements, memoranda and circulated documents, 1941-1947 (Folder 19: 2)
        Includes "Why Hoover Is Wrong" and other issuances by William Agar and Ulric Bell
      - Printed matter
        - General. Pamphlets, printed articles, clipping, and flyers, mainly opposed to food relief, 1941 (Folder 19: 3)
          Includes Food or Freedom; The Isolationist Illusion; The Isolationist Illusion and World Peace; Shall the Small Invaded Nations Be Fed?; Should Britain Relax Her Food Blockade for Hitler's Victims?; Why?
        - Genung, A. B., Food Policies during World War II, 1951 (Folder 19: 4)
    - Commission for Relief in Belgium issuances. "The Peril of Starvation" (circulated compilation of documents) and food maps, 1940 (Folder 19: 5)
    - National Committee on Food for the Five Small Democracies. Press releases, 1940 (Folder 19: 6)
    - Fight for Freedom Committee issuances (opposed to food relief). Press releases, circulated documents, and printed appeals, 1941 (Folder 19: 7)
    - Student Defenders of Democracy issuances (opposed to food relief). Bulletins and leaflets, 1941 (Folder 19: 8)
  - France
    - General. Bulletins and pamphlet, 1941-ca. 1945 (Folder 20: 1)
    - Bonnet, Georges. Letter and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1946-1949 (Folder 20: 2)
    - Reynaud, Paul. Letter and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1947-1949 (Folder 20: 3)
  - Germany
    - General
      - General. Memoranda, clippings, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1942-1953 (Folder 20: 4)
      - Pamphlets, 1938-1939 (Folder 20: 5)
        Includes Building the Third Reich; In Quest of Empire; Shadow over Europe
    - Anti-Nazi resistance, 1942-1946 (Folder 20: 6)
      Pamphlet (Die Tragödie des 20 Juli 1944) and typed transcripts of reports, letters, speeches, and writings by and about German resistance figures, including Karl Gördeler, and including documentation of the 1944 attempt to assassinate Adolf Hitler
    - Dulles, Allen W. Memorandum and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1947 (Folder 20: 7)
    - Grenfell, Russell. Memorandum and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1953 (Folder 20: 8)
    - Hassell, Ulrich von. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1947 (Folder 20: 9)
    - Hitler, Adolf. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1939-1946 (Folder 20: 10)
    - Liddell Hart, B. H. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1948 (Folder 20: 11)
    - Nuremberg War Crime Trials. Memoranda, notes, and excerpts from trial testimony, 1945-1949 (Folder 20: 12)
    - Schmidt, Paul. Memoranda and printed articles, 1950 (Folder 20: 13)
  - Great Britain
    - General. Flyers, pamphlets, speeches, clippings, printed articles, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1934-1953 (Folder 21: 1)
      Includes English Opinion of America; Social Insurance
    - Chamberlain, Neville. Memorandum, clipping, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1940-1946 (Folder 21: 2)
    - Churchill, Winston. Memoranda, clippings, printed articles, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1929-1954 (Folder 21: 3-4)
    - Cripps, Sir Stafford. Clippings and printed articles, 1942-1945 (Folder 21: 5)
    - Hankey, Lord Maurice. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1950 (Folder 21: 6)
    - Winant, John G. Memorandum and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1947 (Folder 21: 7)
  - Italy. Ciano, Galeazzo. Memoranda and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1949-1952 (Folder 21: 8)
  - Japan
    - General
      - Memoranda, letter, notes, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1941-1953 (Folder 22: 1)
      - Clippings and printed articles, 1940-1955 (Folder 22: 2)
    - Butow, Robert J. C. Memoranda, clipping, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1953-1954 (Folder 22: 3)
    - Feis, Herbert. Memoranda, notes, and printed excerpts, 1950-1952 (Folder 22: 4)
    - Grenfell, Russell. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1951 (Folder 22: 5)
    - Grew, Joseph C. Memoranda, notes, typed excerpts from printed sources, clippings, and booklet (Report from Tokyo), 1942-1952 (Folder 22: 6)
    - Hull, Cordell. Memoranda and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1948-1949 (Folder 22: 7)
    - International Military Tribunal for the Far East
      - Memoranda and typed excerpts from testimony and documents introduced as evidence, 1946-1949 (Folder 22: 8)
      - Memoranda and typed excerpts from testimony and documents introduced as evidence (contd.), 1946-1949 (Folder 23: 1)
      - Typed excerpts from judicial opinions, 1948 (Folder 23: 2)
    - Kase, Tashikazu. Clipping and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1950 (Folder 23: 3)
    - Konoye, Prince Fumimaro. Letters, memoranda, clippings, and typed excerpts from memoirs, 1936-1953 (Folder 23: 4)
      Includes letters by Bonner Fellers and photocopy of letter by Konoye
    - MacArthur, Douglas. Memorandum, report on interview of MacArthur, clippings, and printed articles, 1948-1955 (Folder 23: 5)
    - Morgenstern, George. Memorandum, clippings, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1947 (Folder 23: 6)
    - Stimson, Henry L. Correspondence between Stimson and Herbert Hoover, draft diplomatic messages, memorandum by Payson J. Treat, notes, and typed excerpts from printed diary, 1931-1948 (Folder 23: 7)
    - Tansill, Charles C. Clippings and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1952 (Folder 24: 1)
    - Theobald, Robert A. Memoranda, 1953 (Folder 24: 2)
    - United States. Congress. Joint Committee on the Investigation of the Pearl Harbor Attack, 1946 (Folder 24: 3)
      Typed excerpts from printed proceedings
    - United States. Department of State. Memorandum and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1943-1949 (Folder 24: 4)
    - Zacharias, Ellis M. (re atomic bomb). Memoranda, printed articles, clippings, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1945-1950 (Folder 24: 5)
  - Lend-lease operations. Correspondence, memoranda, notes, press releases, clippings, and printed reports of the Lend-Lease Administrator, 1941-1945 (Folder 24: 6-7)
  - Naval strength. Memoranda, notes, and statistics, 1947-1950 (Folder 24: 8)
  - Oil industry
    - General. Letter by Herbert Hoover, Jr., speeches, printed articles, and pamphlets, 1944-1945 (Folder 24: 9)
      Includes Anglo-American Oil Agreement; Oil and the Americas; Petroleum and American Foreign Policy; World Oil: Fact and Policy
    - United States. Petroleum Industry War Council issuances. Press releases, circulated documents, and pamphlets, 1944 (Folder 25: 1)
      Includes A Foreign Oil Policy for the United States; A National Oil Policy for the United States; United States Foreign Oil Policy and Petroleum Reserves Corporation
  - Poland
    - Anders, Wladyslaw. Memoranda and printed excerpts, 1953 (Folder 25: 2)
    - Ciechanowski, Jan. Clipping and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1947 (Folder 25: 3)
    - Katyn Forest Massacre. Clippings and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1950-1952 (Folder 25: 4)
    - Lane, Arthur Bliss. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1948 (Folder 25: 5)
    - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1948 (Folder 25: 6)
  - Postwar planning
    - General. Clippings, bulletins, printed articles, and pamphlets, 1942-1953 (Folder 25: 7-8)
      Includes Peace Plans and American Choices; Take Your Place at the Peace Table
    - Post War World Council issuances. Bulletins and pamphlet, 1942 (Folder 25: 9)
  - Soviet Union
    - General. Clipping and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1936-1948 (Folder 26: 1)
    - Beloff, Max. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1947-1949 (Folder 26: 2)
    - Dallin, David J. Letters and memoranda, 1949 (Folder 26: 3)
    - Deane, John R. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1946-1947 (Folder 26: 4)
    - Krivitsky, Walter. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1939 (Folder 26: 5)
    - Stalin, Joseph. Typed quotations from printed sources, 1934-1945 (Folder 26: 6)
    - Taracouzio, T. A. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1940 (Folder 26: 7)
  - Spain. Hayes, Carlton J. H. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1945 (Folder 26: 8)
  - Unconditional surrender policy. Memoranda, clippings, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1941-1949 (Folder 26: 9)
    Includes United States Department of State memorandum of Atlantic Charter conference
  - United Nations declaration reaffirming Atlantic Charter, 1942 (Folder 26: 10)
  - United States
    - Economy. Material on wartime American economy in connection with what Herbert Hoover regarded as "mismanagement of the war"
      - General
        - Letters, notes, memoranda, and statistical data, 1941-1943 (Folder 26: 11)
        - Press releases and speeches, 1938-1945 (Folder 26: 12-13)
        - Printed articles and clippings, 1941-1945 (Folder 27: 1)
        - Pamphlets, 1935-1945 (Folder 27: 2)
          Includes The American Way: Business Freedom or Government Control?; Conditions of International Monetary Equilibrium; Curtailment of Non-Defense Expenditures; Hard Money; Socialism: The Slave State; The United States in a New World: The Domestic Economy
        - Serial issues and bulletins, 1939-1945 (Folder 27: 3-4)
      - Clark, Fred G., and Richard Stanton Rimanoczy, How We Live: A Simple Dissection of the Economic Body, 1944 (Folder 28: 1)
        Printed copy with synopsis and advertising material
      - Economists' National Committee on Monetary Policy issuances. Bulletins, circulated documents, and pamphlets, 1940-1945 (Folder 28: 2)
        Includes Allied Military Currency; The Manipulation of Our Federal Reserve Bank Notes
      - The Individualist. Serial issues, 1944 (Folder 28: 3)
      - National Association of Manufacturers issuances. Press releases, speeches, and pamphlets, 1941-1945 (Folder 28: 4)
        Includes American Women at War; Health on the Production Front; Men against Time; Production for Victory
      - National Industrial Conference Board issuances. Speeches, bulletins, reports, almanacs, and pamphlets, 1935-1945 (Folder 28: 5)
        Includes A Critical Analysis of the Meany-Thomas Report on the Cost of Living; Government's Place in Post-War Labor-Management Relations; Measuring and Projecting National Income; The Pattern of Inflation; Reducing Fluctuations in Employment; Social Security: An Analysis of the Wagner-Murray Bill; Social Security: Its Present and Future Fiscal Aspects; Trends in Company Pension Plans; The World's Biggest Business: American Public Spending, 1914-1944
      - National Industrial Conference Board issuances (contd.) (Folder 29: 1-3)
      - United States government issuances (miscellaneous). Press releases and statistics, 1942-1943 (Folder 29: 4)
      - United States Congressional issuances (miscellaneous). Press releases, speeches, and reports, 1941-1944 (Folder 29: 5)
      - United States. Congress. Joint Committee on Reduction of Nonessential Federal Expenditures. Press releases and reports, 1942-1945 (Folder 29: 6)
      - United States. Congress. Senate. Special Committee Investigating the National Defense Program. Reports, 1942-1943 (Folder 30: 1)
    - Foreign policy
      - General. Essays, reports, memoranda, printed articles, pamphlets, and bulletins, 1941-1945 (Folder 30: 2-3)
        Includes "Objectives and their Implications to Which We Have Been Committed" and The 1944 Report, authorship of both unattributed
      - Bullitt, William C. Printed articles and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1946 (Folder 30: 4)
      - Byrnes, James F. Memorandum, printed article, clippings, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1946-1952 (Folder 30: 5)
      - Citizens for Victory. Letters, printed appeals, circulated documents, and list of sponsors, 1942 (Folder 30: 6)
      - Committee for National Morale. Booklet (White Book of the United States Foreign Policy, 1932-1942) and list of sponsors (Folder 30: 7)
      - Current, Richard N. Typed transcript of printed article, 1954 (Folder 30: 8)
      - Dennis, Lawrence. Bulletins (Weekly Foreign Letter), 1942 (Folder 30: 9)
      - Farley, James A. Printed article and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1947-1948 (Folder 30: 10)
      - Federal Union. Memoranda, printed appeals, leaflets, and clippings, 1941-1942 (Folder 30: 11)
      - Forrestal, James. Clippings, memorial service booklet, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1951 (Folder 30: 12)
      - Garner, John Nance. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1948 (Folder 31: 1)
      - Hopkins, Harry. Memoranda, clipping, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1941-1950 (Folder 31: 2)
      - Hull, Cordell. Correspondence between Hull and Herbert Hoover, memoranda, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1940-1948 (Folder 31: 3)
      - Kennedy, Joseph P. Letter, memoranda, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1940-1951 (Folder 31: 4)
      - Langer, William L., and S. Everett Gleason. Memoranda and printed excerpts, 1952 (Folder 31: 5)
      - Morgenthau, Henry, Jr. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1947 (Folder 31: 6)
      - Perkins, Frances. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1946 (Folder 31: 7)
      - Phillips, William. Typed excerpts from printed sources, 1952 (Folder 31: 8)
      - Roosevelt, Franklin D. Memoranda, clippings, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1923-1955 (Folder 31: 9)
      - Sanborn, Frederic R. Printed excerpts, 1951 (Folder 31: 10)
      - Stimson, Henry L. Memoranda, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1939-1952 (Folder 31: 11)
      - Vandenberg, Arthur H. Memoranda, clippings, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1952 (Folder 31: 12)
      - Welles, Sumner. Memoranda, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1941-1951 (Folder 32: 1)
    - Income. Statistics, circulated documents, and radio broadcast transcript, 1940-1945 (Folder 32: 2)
    - Inflation. Clippings, printed articles, pamphlet, and typescripts, 1938-1945 (Folder 32: 3)
    - Labor and employment. Memorandum, statistics, circulated documents, printed articles, and pamphlets, 1941-1945 (Folder 32: 4-5)
      Includes Collective Bargaining; The Harry Bridges Case; and draft manpower and employment bills
    - Neutrality
      - General. Memorandum, circulated documents, and pamphlet, 1940-1941 (Folder 32: 6)
        Includes America Answers Lindbergh!; The Consequences of a Democratic Victory; Footprints of the Trojan Horse
      - America First Committee. Bulletins, circulated documents, speeches, and clippings, 1940-1941 (Folder 32: 7)
      - Keep America Out of War Congress. Bulletins, circulated documents, and pamphlet (Conscription and Liberty), 1941 (Folder 33: 1)
      - Townsend, Ralph. Pamphlets, 1938-1940 (Folder 33: 2)
        Includes The High Cost of Hate; Seeking Foreign Trouble; There Is No Halfway Neutrality!
    - Politics
      - General. Letter, circulated documents, leaflets, pamphlets, speeches, and printed articles, 1938-1945 (Folder 33: 3)
        Includes Flagrant Misrepresentations at the Democratic Convention of 1944; For Our City; The Roots of Liberty; Three Talks on Freedom; Why Race Riots?
      - American System Council. Bylaws and pamphlets, 1940 (Folder 33: 4)
        Includes The American System; Dominism
      - National Foundation for Education in American Citizenship. Pamphlets, 1940-1945 (Folder 33: 5)
        Includes Political Parties; A Proposal for Better Citizenship and More Capable Administration in Government
      - Republican Party Mackinac Conference, 1943 (Folder 33: 6)
        Herbert Hoover correspondence, agenda, memoranda, press releases, and clippings
      - Union for Democratic Action. Bylaws, press releases, and circulated documents, 1942-1945 (Folder 34: 1)
    - Price controls